Guide to The Packer Collegiate Institute records 2014.019
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 17: Photographs, 1845-circa 2010; 58 Cubic Feet
  - Sub-series 17.1: Packer Collegiate Institute photographs, circa 1850-circa 2010; 50 Cubic Feet in 107 boxes
    - Statue of Liberty Chapel, February 29 – Summer Pizza party, 1984 (Box 300, Folder 10)
    - Garden, 1984 (Box 304, Folder 16)
    - Students, 1984 (Box 526, Folder 12)
    - Grandparents Day, May 1984 (Box 391, Folder 32)
    - Atlantic Antic, October 1984 (Box 391, Folder 33)
    - Latin projects / Central America afternoon discussion, November 1984 (Box 391, Folder 34)
    - Lower School Winter Sing, December 1984 (Box 391, Folder 35)
    - Turner - 3rd grade / Christmas pageant and music / Chanukah Chapel, December 1984 (Box 391, Folder 36)
    - Grammar Busters awards / Brodie - English / Sklarsky, December 1984 (Box 391, Folder 37)
    - Santa Claus and Spirit of Christmas Kindergarten illegible, December 1984 (Box 391, Folder 38)
    - Holiday Sing in church, December 1984 (Box 391, Folder 39)
    - Music assembly in church / Middle School chorus, brass, Riggio, December 1984 (Box 391, Folder 40)
    - Atlantic Antic, 1985 (Box 391, Folder 41)
    - May Day, 1985 (Box 308, Folder 4)
    - Drawing of Packer Entrance - Oversize, 1985 (Box 547, Folder -)
    - Gymnastics assembly, January 1985 (Box 391, Folder 42)
    - Dr. Ranck (Brain) Schindel / Middle School show "Tarradiddle Travels", January 1985 (Box 391, Folder 43)
    - Bulgarian (students talk) Ippolito and Koplowitz / garden snow fights, February 1985 (Box 391, Folder 44)
    - Bulgarian (students talk) Ippolito and Koplowitz / garden snow fights, February 1985 (Box 391, Folder 45)
    - Middle School Science - Travis (8), overlap pictures of gymnastics, Solarz, February 1985 (Box 391, Folder 46)
    - Bulgarian dance troupe / Ken Rush lecture, February 1985 (Box 391, Folder 47)
    - Middle School teachers and students in classrooms / Hitchman (6th grade science), Roos (8th grade math), Marshall (6th grade English), February 1985 (Box 391, Folder 48)
    - Bulgarian dance troupe / Packer dancers, February 1985 (Box 391, Folder 49)
    - Senior Slump pizza party / Toga Day / Girls Basketball team / Language Week in Front Hall / Tulloch taking to PTA / poetry contest, March 1985 (Box 391, Folder 50)
    - Garden basketball game / Seniors in window / Wenger and Schulhof 4th grade classes prep for International Fair / Karasik HR intro / Karasik sculpture class in garden, March 1985 (Box 391, Folder 51)
    - Girls basketball game / 5th grade write in, March 1985 (Box 391, Folder 52)
    - Middle School students versus faculty basketball game, March 1985 (Box 391, Folder 53)
    - Chris d'Amboise Chapel program, March 1985 (Box 391, Folder 54)
    - Chris d'Amboise Chapel program / Inger Kristensen Lower School science lesson, March 1985 (Box 391, Folder 55)
    - Human Rights write-in / 5th grade pinata / Middle School students versus faculty basketball game, March 1985 (Box 391, Folder 56)
    - Human Rights day / Esty / Caubochaino (?) gay rights / Sally Krause Lower School bake sale, March 1985 (Box 391, Folder 57)
    - Judo demonstration / International Fair, April 1985 (Box 391, Folder 58)
      Marsh
    - Jump Rope for Heart event, May 1985 (Box 391, Folder 59)
    - Packer Plus / NYU dance / Gorelick (French) / Gurreri (gym), May 1985 (Box 391, Folder 60)
    - Dance / ballet master class, May 1985 (Box 391, Folder 61)
    - Maypole dance / Alumni reunion, May 1985 (Box 391, Folder 62)
    - 8th grade history (Golston) / 2nd grade / Gina Caruso / poetry / Robillard, May 1985 (Box 391, Folder 63)
    - Lower School - Reiss, Krause, Mednick, Ayouf, Ju(?) in Human Resources, Arbolino, Felix and Joe / front of Packer building, May 1985 (Box 391, Folder 64)
    - Library / Kristiansen / Synott parent 4th grade, May 1985 (Box 391, Folder 65)
    - Alumni reunion, May 1985 (Box 391, Folder 66)
    - Packer Plus, gymnastics (Gurreri) / science (Hitchman) / Art (Baylin), May 1985 (Box 391, Folder 67)
    - Battle of Ages, May 1985 (Box 391, Folder 68)
    - 8th grade (John Sexton) / 8th grade History (Golston) / Maypole dance / New York University (NYU) Law, May 1985 (Box 391, Folder 69)
    - Packer Plus, Brick / French / Origami, May 1985 (Box 391, Folder 70)
    - Lower School puppet show (Krause, Baylin) / Battle of Ages, May 1985 (Box 391, Folder 71)
    - English (Brodie) / Physical Education (Britton and Quigley) / librarians Berger and Burger, May 1985 (Box 391, Folder 72)
    - Graduation, June 12, 1985 (Box 391, Folder 73)
      Scott
    - Packer summer, July 1985 (Box 391, Folder 74)
    - Academic awards in Chapel, July 1985 (Box 391, Folder 75)
    - Atlantic Antic / Jim Chopin / Esty at desk / Graduation in Chapel / Martine and Gilli Wedon, September 1985 (Box 391, Folder 76)
    - Pumpkin Patch, October 1985 (Box 391, Folder 77)
    - Young Alumni Night, November 1985 (Box 391, Folder 78)
    - Senior party night / Brass choir / performing at senior citizens center / Paul Riggio, November 1985 (Box 391, Folder 79)
    - Dance master class / music in Chapel / Laura Dean / Bernsteiner / Chris Agee / Martin Agee / Paul Riggio, November 1985 (Box 391, Folder 80)
    - Chanukah chapel / choral concert / Patty Catena chapel talk, December 1985 (Box 391, Folder 81)
    - New Christmas Pageant (1 of 2), December 1985 (Box 391, Folder 82)
    - New Christmas Pageant (2 of 2), December 1985 (Box 391, Folder 83)
    - Girls basketball game / Students versus faculty volleyball game, December 1985 (Box 391, Folder 84)
    - Choral concert / Joan Wenger and 4th graders waiting for next class / Carol Silver telling stories to Carol Schulthof's 4th graders / Lower School Sing, December 1985 (Box 391, Folder 85)
    - Publication photos, circa 1985-2000 (Box 406, Folder 24)
    - Luncheon event, circa 1985-2000 (Box 406, Folder 25)
      Contact sheet
    - Events – Alumni Reunion, 1986 (Box 300, Folder 9)
    - Yearbook Photographs – Art, Music, Theater, 1986 (Box 219, Folder 15)
    - Yearbook Photographs, Individual Students, 1986 (Box 219, Folder 16)
    - Yearbook Photographs, Faculty, 1986 (Box 219, Folder 17)
    - Yearbook - Small group photos, 1986 (Box 220, Folder 1)
    - Yearbook - Group photos, 1986 (Box 220, Folder 2)
    - Yearbook Photographs, Sports, 1986 (Box 220, Folder 3)
    - Yearbook Photographs, Oversize, 1986 (Box 221, Folder 1)
    - Yearbook layouts, Oversize, 1986 (Box 221, Folder 2)
    - Yearbook Photographs, individual shots of the Senior Class and negatives of senior group shots, Oversize, 1986 (Box 221, Folder 3)
    - Art of Persuasion student speakers / Peter Esty / Faculty dance, January 1986 (Box 391, Folder 87)
    - Peter Esty - witchcraft / Babbott Chair holders / Martin Luther King (MLK) dance program / Dan Laphan /, January 1986 (Box 391, Folder 88)
    - Martin Luther King Chapel program, January 1986 (Box 391, Folder 89)
    - Rev. Melish / Stacy Greendlinger (?) / Brass choir, February 1986 (Box 391, Folder 90)
    - Nicaragua speakers and media interviews / McNeill Lehrer television interview / WBAI/Brooklyn Paper reporter's interview / Scott Brody speak on Nicaragua, February 1986 (Box 391, Folder 91)
    - Dance Concert / "Assume the Position" / Faculty Piece, February 1986 (Box 391, Folder 92)
    - Dance Concert Rehearsal, February 1986 (Box 391, Folder 93)
    - Dance Concert Performance / Kuizel / Group Dance (James Dean) / Junior Varsity Boys Basketball, February 1986 (Box 391, Folder 94)
    - Junior Varsity Boys Basketball / Britton talks to Varsity Boys Basketball / McNeil Lehrer Interview, February 1986 (Box 391, Folder 95)
    - Karen Brody / Senior Pizza Party with Alumni / Nicaragua Speaker Scott Brody, March 1986 (Box 391, Folder 96)
    - Science Fair / Peter Esty / Gogshots (?) by Eyster, April 1986 (Box 391, Folder 97)
    - Babbott Lecture Gold / 4th Grade International Fair, April 1986 (Box 391, Folder 98)
    - Boys from Syracuse Chapel / Middle School/Upper School Original Writing in Chapel, April 1986 (Box 391, Folder 99)
    - Variety of School Shots / Brodie (English) / Parents Day / Upper School Student Center / Senior Homeroom, April - May 1986 (Box 391, Folder 100)
    - Alumni Teachers at Packer, May 1986 (Box 391, Folder 101)
    - Hudson Shatz / Chiara Anderson / student art painted on building, May 1986 (Box 391, Folder 102)
    - Grandparents Day, May 1986 (Box 391, Folder 103)
    - Mets Game Scoreboards (Carole McKinney), May 1986 (Box 391, Folder 104)
    - Music Chapel / Garden / Upper School Student Lounge, May 1986 (Box 391, Folder 105)
    - Record Shots / Packer Plaques / front garden flags, May 1986 (Box 391, Folder 106)
    - Science Fair / Blood Drive, May 8, 1986 (Box 391, Folder 107)
    - Gate presentation / Esty, Wadsworth, Stutt / Lower School Kids (Christine Bongiorno), June 1986 (Box 391, Folder 108)
    - Bill Bendel / Tom Cook Interview / Annual Giving / AFS Marie Aunor (?) / ESU Callie Wordsworth, September 1986 (Box 391, Folder 109)
    - Mike Shaffer - 8th Grade History / Cotton Ball Demonstration, September 1986 (Box 391, Folder 110)
    - School Opening / Upper School Lounge / Middle School new students / Front Lobby / Chapel / 3rd Grade, September 1986 (Box 391, Folder 111)
    - School Opening / Levine and Esty / Upper School Student Center / Front Lobby / New Faculty, September 1986 (Box 391, Folder 112)
    - School Opening / Joyce Houston With Kids, September 1986 (Box 391, Folder 113)
    - Koplowitz 42nd Street / Kick line, September 1986 (Box 391, Folder 114)
    - Brooklyn Heights Press / "Fashion" Photographs, September 24, 1986 (Box 391, Folder 115)
    - Atlantic Antic (Wicke) / Pumpkin Patch (Wicke), October 1986? (Box 391, Folder 116)
    - Pumpkin Patch / Pipes 101 - Wingate, October 1986 (Box 391, Folder 117)
    - 9th Graders / Israel Speaker / Palestine Speaker / Students studying / Tullock, October 1986 (Box 391, Folder 118)
    - Marie Aurore Fox / AFS Daily News / Squash Players / Rashidi Khalidi and Dr. Sturges / Calvin Gooding, October 1986 (Box 391, Folder 119)
    - Unloading pumpkins / 2nd grade school photos / Lazaro - singing, October 1986 (Box 391, Folder 120)
    - Fasano - Braille Show & Tell / Stanton / Miller / Sklarsky / Baylin, October 1986 (Box 391, Folder 121)
    - Great Peace March Speaker / Mets World Series Ticker Tape Parade / Playing in Garden / Cafe Bonjourno (?), October 1986 (Box 391, Folder 122)
    - Sally Snyder - 2nd grade Art / Backstage at "Rimers of Eldritch" / South Africa speaker & Eliz Marshall / Library - students at work, October-November 1986 (Box 391, Folder 123)
    - Palladium party / Founders Day and Reception / Rev. Bill Nye, November 1986 (Box 391, Folder 124)
      Possibly November 1987
    - Founders Day / Palladium / Delmhorst / George Jones, November 1986 (Box 391, Folder 125)
    - "Rimers of Eldritch" theatrical production, November 1986 (Box 391, Folder 126)
    - Novantiqua Renaissance Dance Troupe / Travis, Bailey, Logan, Siegel, Riggio, Roos, Lapham, Cooney, Surkis, 2 kids studying 5th, November 1986 (Box 391, Folder 127)
    - American Cancer Smokeout / Lower School masks, November 1986 (Box 391, Folder 128)
    - Esty reads to 3s - Mary Marsh / 2nd graders give $600 to homeless, December 1986 (Box 392, Folder 1)
    - Chorus and Brass Choir at Pan Am Building & Bus Terminal, December 1986 (Box 392, Folder 2)
      Possibly December 1987
    - Christmas pageant and reception, December 1986 (Box 392, Folder 3)
    - Lower School Winter Sing / Parents visitor reception / Marsh & Autographed Book / Ms. March Singing, December 1986 (Box 392, Folder 4)
    - Brass Choir at World Trade Center, December 1986 (Box 392, Folder 5)
    - Chanukah Chapel / Brass Choir at World Trade Center, December 1986 (Box 392, Folder 6)
    - Awareness Day / Social Action Committee / 2nd grade student (Pike) returns to Thailand / Pageant preperformance / Esty talking to Kings / George Boutis Chapel Talk, December 1986 (Box 392, Folder 7)
    - Snow Dragon in garden / Black History Chapel / Martin Luther King, December 1986 (Box 392, Folder 8)
    - Young Alumni, December 1986 (Box 392, Folder 9)
    - Winter Sing Reception / Senior Homeroom / Eusth (?) working with kids / St. Ann's visit to 2nd graders / Kindergarteners working, December 1986 (Box 392, Folder 10)
    - Girls basketball game vs. St. Ann's / Christmas tournament / Brass Choir at Bus Terminal, December 1986 (Box 392, Folder 11)
    - Event, December 1986 (Box 392, Folder 12)
    - Theatrical production / Denny Bledgets production of "The Boys at Syracuse", 1986-1987 (Box 391, Folder 86)
    - Miscellaneous, 1986-1995 (Box 405, Folder 10)
    - Christmas Pageant / Sam Ross / Carder (?), 1987 (Box 392, Folder 13)
    - Sam Ross / Christmas Pageant, 1987 (Box 392, Folder 14)
    - Students in a classroom, 1987 (Box 392, Folder 15)
      Loose Negatives
    - Yearbook Photographs, clubs and casual groups of students, 1987 (Box 220, Folder 4)
    - Yearbook Photographs, Music, 1987 (Box 220, Folder 5)
    - Yearbook Photographs, Individuals (student), 1987 (Box 220, Folder 6)
    - Yearbook Photographs, non-human, 1987 (Box 220, Folder 7)
    - Yearbook Photographs, Casual Groups Students, 1987 (Box 220, Folder 8)
    - Yearbook Photographs, Class Groups, Lower School, 1987 (Box 220, Folder 9)
    - Yearbook Photographs, Faculty and Staff, 1987 (Box 220, Folder 10)
    - Yearbook Photographs, Sports, 1987 (Box 220, Folder 11)
    - Yearbook Photographs, Drama, 1987 (Box 220, Folder 12)
    - Yearbook layouts, Oversize, 1987 (Box 221, Folder 4)
    - Gymnastics Exhibition, January 1987 (Box 392, Folder 16)
    - Calvin Gooding / Gymnastics Chapel / Rosa Parks Skit / 1st grade gym class parachute, January 1987 (Box 392, Folder 17)
    - Rush & Visual Arts 100 students at Brooklyn Museum / "Storm over Rocky Mountains - Mount Rosalie", January 1987 (Box 392, Folder 18)
    - Ken Rush PTA lecture / George Hanford New York State Association of Independent Schools (NYSAIS) conference, January 1987 and April 1987 (Box 392, Folder 19)
    - Middle School Poetry Program - Caruso, February 1987 (Box 392, Folder 20)
    - Kathleen Hill Dance / "Uninvited Guest" / Esty, Hetzler, etc / Gymnastics Exhibition, February 1987 (Box 392, Folder 21)
    - Senior Home room in Alumni Room / Mike Lacopo, February 1987 (Box 392, Folder 22)
    - Grammar Busters / Sylvia Hewlett / "Uninvited Guest" of Kathleen Hall / Susan Roos, Robert Steen / Dance Poucent (?) Chapel, February 1987 (Box 392, Folder 23)
    - Karen Johnson - Kurt Kalofer doing architectural evaluation of building ('80) / Middle School Theater Art-a-thon / Carol Silver goodbye / Kate Adams Fumark (?) scholar / Carole Silver and Chris Rush, Lower School librarians / David Goodwin, Anne Gregory - Women's History Profiles / Upper School Advertising and sexism panel, March 1987 (Box 392, Folder 24)
    - Schuidel - Art-a-thon / Robillard - French class / Hemingsen - MS Poetry / Glenn Jones + Oman Breval - sweeping up after For Lang Lunch / Gabi Blecher - Senior HR / Brass Choir - Anthem / Ken Rush - after Sexism lecture, March 1987 (Box 392, Folder 25)
    - Tropical Day / Dean Porter talking to Roy Siegel's 5th grade about Star Wars / Trustee photos / Babysitting Course / Nicaragua Speaker / New York State Association of Independent Schools (NYSAIS) Harford Photo / Hemingsen Lecture, March 1987 (Box 392, Folder 26)
    - New York State Association of Independent Schools (NYSAIS) Arts & Thinking Conference / AHS Arts Festival, April 1987 (Box 392, Folder 27)
    - Middle School Science Fair, April 1987 (Box 392, Folder 28)
    - Mock Trial Team / Schoololympics / Agee POQ (?) Bach Performance / Library / McKellen - Jons / Hodad, April 1987 (Box 392, Folder 29)
    - 6th grade Babysitting course / Photo of painting outside Development Office, April 1987 (Box 392, Folder 30)
    - ATIS Arts Festivals / Middle School Dance, Theatre, Music, April 1987 (Box 392, Folder 31)
    - Bob Stein Comedy Winter Follies / Jennifer Blair - Headmaster for Rudy / Middle School Science Fair, April 1987 (Box 392, Folder 32)
    - Trustee Visiting Day / Fasano (Kindergarten) - Dinosaur Lunch / Christine Rush, Carole Silver - Lower School Librarians / Hemingsen talking to English evaluation team / Tropical Day, April 1987 (Box 392, Folder 33)
    - Nicaraguan speakers / Zyguntowicz (?) / 4th grade International Fair, April 1987 (Box 392, Folder 34)
    - New York State Association of Independent Schools (NYSAIS) Arts & Thinking Conference, April 2-3, 1987 (Box 392, Folder 35)
    - May Day, Baylin setup grandparent + grandchild / Stanton, Fasano, Baylin, Dance Masta class / student tying another's shoe, May 1987 (Box 392, Folder 36)
    - Grandparents Day / Outside Dr. Seuss / May Day Maypole Dance, May 1987 (Box 392, Folder 37)
    - Grandparents Day / Grandparents and children, May 1987 (Box 392, Folder 38)
    - May Day Outside / Dr. Seuss of Irana (?) Circus / Grandparents Day, May 1987 (Box 392, Folder 39)
    - Grandparents Day / Mowing (?) Introduction / Grandparents and children / Classroom presentations / Euroth, Krause, Smith, Snyder, May 1987 (Box 392, Folder 40)
    - Babara Feigin (?) Advertising / Talking to Upper School Kids / AFS Kids from Connecticut / Every Flute / Gold and Morgenson / Gold and four Seniors and Esty / May Day / Dr. Seuss, May 1, 1987 (Box 392, Folder 41)
    - Graduation - George Jones / Middle School Talent Show - Esty and Class, May - June 1987 (Box 392, Folder 42)
    - Middle School Talent Show / Mock Trial Plaque / City Champion / Ken Rush - Paintings / Grandparents Day, June 1987 (Box 392, Folder 43)
    - Kiat Oboler, June 1987 (Box 392, Folder 44)
    - Mets / Brass Choir, June 5, 1987 (Box 392, Folder 45)
    - Day Camp polices (?) Joralemon Street / Graduation (Jones), June - July 1987 (Box 392, Folder 46)
    - Day Camp Talent Show, July 1987 (Box 392, Folder 47)
    - Jay Stetges, September 1987 (Box 392, Folder 48)
    - Guy Carden / Pumpkin Patch / Borley (?) Science / Emery and Kids / Karasik and Kids, October 1987 (Box 392, Folder 49)
    - Carden / Pumpkin Patch, October 1987 (Box 392, Folder 50)
    - Carden / Founders Day / Brooklyn Transportation / Middle School Soccer - Donovan (?), November 1987 (Box 392, Folder 51)
      Possibly November 1988
    - Carden / Lower School Gym Class / String Music Performance in Garden, November 1987 (Box 392, Folder 52)
    - Wingate / Boutis / Snyder / Croy / Lewis / Rush, November 1987 (Box 392, Folder 53)
    - Mike Schaffer 6th grade Core / Mosaic Project / Young Alumni Reception, November 1987 (Box 392, Folder 54)
    - Young Alumni Reception, November 1987 (Box 392, Folder 55)
    - Schaffer / 6th Grade / Brooklyn Museum / Mosaics, November 1987 (Box 392, Folder 56)
    - Carden / Dolan Sinake (?), November 1987 (Box 392, Folder 57)
    - Portraits / Bookhout (?) / Heiland / Hungsen (?) / Esty / Franlinson (?) / Wiltshire, November 1987 (Box 392, Folder 58)
    - Pageant / Boys Basketball, December 1987 (Box 392, Folder 59)
      Sam Koss
    - Christmas Pageant Rehearsal / Speaker from M.A.D.R.E. / 3rd Grade Indian Museum Diorama / 4th grade - Wenger, $200 Check, December 1987 (Box 392, Folder 60)
    - Lower School Sing Choral Concert, December 1987 (Box 392, Folder 61)
    - Irene Turner parent fillet fish / 6th grade core - Schaffer / Marshall / 3rd grade - Sally Snyder / Delmhorst, Scafidi cello duet, December 1987 (Box 392, Folder 62)
    - Girls Basketball / Boys Basketball / Christmas Tournament / Dureka Carasquillo (?), December 1987 (Box 392, Folder 63)
    - Pageant / Girls Basketball, December 1987 (Box 392, Folder 64)
      Feigue (?) + Ascencio (?) Kings
    - Lower School Winter Sing and parties, December 1987 (Box 392, Folder 65)
    - Carden / Choral Concert / Wingate, December 1987 (Box 392, Folder 66)
    - Chorus on Montague Street / Christmas Tree lights / Christmas pageant / Chanukah Chapel, December 1987 (Box 392, Folder 67)
      Ilford (?)
    - Chanukah Chapel, December 1987 (Box 392, Folder 68)
    - World Trade Center / Chorus and Orchestra at Pan Am Building, December 1987 (Box 392, Folder 69)
    - Chorus and Orchestra at Pan Am Building / Hadad French (?) Carols / Young Alumni, December 1987 (Box 392, Folder 70)
    - Chorus and Orchestra at Pan Am Building, December 1987 (Box 392, Folder 71)
    - 3 bad shots / Christmas pageant audience / Esty / basketball, December 1987 (Box 392, Folder 72)
      Possibly December 1988
    - Carden / Pageant, December 1987 (Box 392, Folder 73)
    - Carden / Judo / Pageant, December 1987 (Box 392, Folder 74)
      Sam Koss / Close Up
    - World Trade Center / Chorus and Orchestra at Pan Am Building, December 1987 (Box 392, Folder 75)
    - Lower School Winter Sing, December 1987 (Box 392, Folder 76)
    - Chorus on Montague Street / Christmas Tree lighting / Wingate rehearsing Kings / 3rd grade Indian Museum / Gave Jason to Jason, December 1987 (Box 392, Folder 77)
      Ilford
    - Mock Trial Team (1988 NYC Championship Winners) (Box 315, Folder 5)
    - Students – Photographer, Sarah Ross/1988 Samples and Prices (Box 315, Folder 11)
    - Yearbook Photographs, Student Activities, 1988 (Box 220, Folder 13)
    - Yearbook Photographs, Sports, 1988 (Box 220, Folder 14)
    - Yearbook Photographs, faculty and staff, 1988 (Box 220, Folder 15)
    - Publication photographs, 1988 (Box 406, Folder 27)
    - Class of 1988 handprints (Box 406, Folder 28)
    - Publication photographs, 1988 (Box 406, Folder 29)
    - Art restoration photos / Alonzo Crittenden portrait, 1988 (Box 526, Folder 13)
    - Students, 1988 (Box 526, Folder 14)
    - Photographs of students, 1988 (Box 526, Folder 15)
      Tom Callan
    - 88-1 Carden / Quigley and basketball / Channel 11 - Sturges / Upper School Lounge - Brodie / Kids / Malcolm Lee - Martin Luther King (MLK) program / Black History, January 1988 (Box 392, Folder 79)
    - 88-2 8th grade leadership / Upper School exams / Young Alumni at Brewery, January 1988 (Box 392, Folder 80)
    - 88-3 Lois Lowry, January 1988 (Box 392, Folder 81)
    - 88-4 4th grade school of Richardson and Stormback / Faison (?) Chapel, January 1988 (Box 392, Folder 82)
    - 88-5 Lois Lowry, January 1988 (Box 392, Folder 83)
    - 88-6 Middle School Girls Basketball / Andrew Marron Libeitar(?) Candidate / Koplowitz / Dance in Chapel, January 1988 (Box 392, Folder 84)
    - 88-7 Carden / Jones Library / Garden Basketball / Upper School studying / little kids playing in sand / Middle School Art-a-thon / Upper School Watch Channel / Paula Bernstein - Martin Luther King (MLK) Day, January 1988 (Box 392, Folder 85)
    - 88-8 4th grade - Schulof (?) / Mrs Richardson NY / Sheila Steinback, Channel 9 / 2nd grade play - Meduck (?) / Maine Coast Semester Director / Esty and Martin Luther King bust / Martin Luther King program, chorus (Wingate) / 2nd grade semester (?) / Tom Cook talk, January 1988 (Box 392, Folder 86)
    - 88-9 Alumni Party at Manhattan Brewery / Upper School exams in Student Lounge / Brewer Chapel Talk / Chair (?) Anderson (?) Chapel Interview / Soccer team recognition - Donovan (?), January 1988 (Box 392, Folder 87)
    - 88-10 2nd grade (Smith ?) art project / Computer, Wallace Brick / McNeil Lehrer, January 1988 (Box 392, Folder 88)
    - 88-11 Trustee Day / Lower School / 3rd grade Science / 3rd grade play rehearsal of "Christopher Columbus" / 2nd grade in Dev/ Malkin Race / no Treat (?) in Lower School / Upper School Lounge, February 1988 (Box 392, Folder 89)
    - 88-12 Agee PDQ Bach / Upper School Student-Faculty Mixer, February 1988 (Box 392, Folder 90)
    - 88-13 Tropical Day / Dance Concert / Carden, February 1988 (Box 392, Folder 91)